Guide to the Stanford University, Center for Latin American Studies, Records SC0185
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Additional Records, circa 1985-2005; Accession ARCH-2010-106
  - Visiting Scholars, Subseries 9
    - Mauricio Tenorio (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Kimberly Theidon 01-02 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Christian Toloza (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Fernando Toledo (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Tonci Tomic 4/98-6/98 Environmental Policy Fellow (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Maria Celia Toro (Fulbright) Apr-Jul 1990 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Helgio Trindade (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Mario Rolf Treuherz June 01-02 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Maria Lucia Vasconcelos (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Sebastiao Velasco E Cruz 7/95-7/96 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Stephen J. Wager (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Georgina Waylen (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Ruben Zamora (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Ruben Zamora 1996 tax (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Ruben Zamora 6/96 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Ruben Zamora Visiting Scholar Research 94-95 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Zerda, Alvaro Visiting Scholar 98-99 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Paula Zuniga (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Enrique Collazos Perez (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Ze Carlos (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Raquel Gamus (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Francisco Weffort (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Wayne Cornelius (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - Philip Oxhorn, McGill University (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - Maria Fernanda Arias 94-95 (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - Jeff Rubin 93-94 (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - Jose Augusto Guilhon - Albuquerque (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - Anna Luiza Ozorio de Almeida (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - Efrain Gonzalez de Olarte Winter 1992 (Box 16, Folder 41)
    - Salvador Avila (Graduate Summer Field Research 2002) (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Graduate Summer Field Research, Subseries 10
    - Vanessa Frank (Law) 02 Grad Summer Field Research grants (Box 16, Folder 43)
    - Steven Gelber 02 Grad Summer Field Research grants ANSI (Box 16, Folder 44)
    - Jacquie Pratt (Earth and Sciences) grad Summer field Research 2002 (Box 16, Folder 45)
    - Gabriel Weintraub (Management Science and Engineering) Grad Summer Field Research 02 (Box 16, Folder 46)
    - Jeffrey Marshall (Education) Graduate Summer Field Research 2002 (Box 16, Folder 47)
    - Lauren Buckley (Biological Sciences) Graduate Summer Field Research 02 (Box 16, Folder 48)
    - Agustin Manuel Paulin (Education) Grad Summer Field Research 02 (Box 16, Folder 49)
    - Graduate Grants Report Summer 2001 (Box 16, Folder 50)
    - Beatriz Camarena (Law School) 2001 Summer Field Research grants (Box 16, Folder 51)
    - Ericka Beckman (Span. and Port.) 2001 Summer Field Research (Box 16, Folder 52)
    - Christen Smith (Cult. And Society Anthropology) 2001 Summ Fld Research (Box 16, Folder 53)
    - Joao Pinho de Mello (Economics) 2001 Summer Field Research grants (Box 16, Folder 54)
    - Cristobal Huneeus (Economics) 2001 Summ Fld Research grants (Box 16, Folder 55)
    - Dana Jensen (Anth Sciences) (Box 16, Folder 56)
    - 2001 Summ Fld Research grants (Box 16, Folder 57)
    - Vernita Lea Ediger (Anthr Sciences) 2001 Summer Field Research (Box 16, Folder 58)
    - Graduate Summer Field Research 2001 (Box 16, Folder 59)
    - I am William Read (History) 2001 Summer Field Research (Box 16, Folder 60)
    - Karen Sue Rolph (Anthro. Sciences) 2001 Summer Field Research (Box 16, Folder 61)
    - Marcia Ochoa (Cult. & Soc. Anthro) 2001 Summer Fld Research (Box 16, Folder 62)
    - Katherine Unterman (Law School) 2001 Summ Field Research grants (Box 16, Folder 63)
    - Robert McMilan (Economics) 2001 Summ Field Research grants (Box 16, Folder 64)
    - Josh Wallenstein (Law) 2001 Summ Fld Research (Box 16, Folder 65)
    - Monica Hurtado (CLAS) 2001 Summ Fld Research (Box 16, Folder 66)
    - Karina Alejandra Hodoyan (Span & Port) 2001 Summ Fld Research (Box 16, Folder 67)
    - Aldo Musacchio (History) 2001 Summ Fld Research grants (Box 16, Folder 68)
    - John Wolf (Anthr. Sciences) 2001 Summer Fld Research Grants (Box 16, Folder 69)
    - Summer Field Research Reports Summer 2000 (Box 16, Folder 70)
    - 2000 Graduate Summer Field Research Grants (Box 16, Folder 71)
    - 2000 Graduate Summer Field Research (Box 16, Folder 72)
    - Human Subjects Protocol (Box 16, Folder 73)
    - Anne E. Egger (Earth & Sciences) Field Research Grants Summer 00 (Box 16, Folder 74)
    - Itamar Grunstein (Medicine) Field Research Grants Summer 2000 (Box 16, Folder 75)
    - Ericka Beckman (Span and Port) Field Research Grants Summer 00 (Box 16, Folder 76)
    - Adrian James (Mechanical Eng) Field Research grants Summer 00 (Box 16, Folder 77)
    - Laura Lopez Hoffman (Biology) Field Research grants Summer 00 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Biasha Mitchell – Field Research grants summer 00 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Andre de Mello (Poli Sci) Graduate Research grants Summer 00 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Francisco Monaldi (Poli Sci) Field Research grants Summer 00 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - William Perez (Education) Field Research grants Summer 00 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Amanda Risser (Medicine) Field Research grants Summer 00 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Carlos Roseman (Anthro Sciences) Field Research grants summer 00 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Sara Rondinel (Span and Port) Field Research grants Summ 00 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Lise Sedrez (Summer 2000) Field Research grants (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Bobby Vaughn (Anthropological Sciences fld. Research 2000) (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Victor White Graduate Research grants Summer 2000 (Cult. Anthrop) (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - John W. Wolf (Anthro Sci.) Field Research Grants Summer 00 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Shannon Moffett (Medicine) Field Research grants Summer 00 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Timothy King (Anthro Sci) Field Research Grants Summer 00 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Robert Buch (Comp. Lit) Field Research grants Summer 2000 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Pedro Cabiya Field Research grants Summer 00 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Carrie Fathman (Urban Studies) Field Research grants Summer 00 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Kelly Freidenfelds (So. Anthro.) Field Research grants Summer 00 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Karina Hodoyan (Span and Port) Field Research grants Summer 00 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Damian Keller Summer 2000 Field Research Grants (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Marcia Ochoa Field Research (Cult & Social Anthropology Summer 2000) (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Carlos G. Suarez (Poli. Sci.) Field Research grants Summer 00 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Glenn Valenzuela (Medicine) Field Research grants Summer 00 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Manuel Vargas (Philosophy) Field Research grants Summer 00 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Graduate Summer Field Research 98-99 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - 1999 Summer Field Research (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Summer Field Research 1999 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Ericka Beckman: 1999 Research Grant (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Hewlett Report Summer Field 1998-1999 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Summer Field Research 2000 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Jessica Aaron (LAS) Field Research Grants Summer 1999 (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Lesley Barnhorn (Law) Field Research Grants Summer 1999 (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Alison Bidwell (Anthro Sciences) Field Research Grants Summer 1999 (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - Michelle Evelyn (Biological Sciences) Field Research Grants Summer 1999 (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - Tasha Fairfield (LAS) Field Research Grants Summer 1999 (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - Shoshanna Lurie (Span & Port) Field Research Grants Summer 1999 (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - Alma Rosa Martinez (Drama) Field Research Grants Summer 1999 (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - Adeunice Mata (Medicine) Field Research Grants Summer 1999 (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - Joel Eduardo Mata (Medicine) Field Research Grants Summer 1999 (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - Jill Medrano (Anthro Sciences) Field Research Grants Summer 1999 (Box 17, Folder 40)
    - Raquel Mendieta (Span & Port) Field Research Grants Summer 1999 (Box 17, Folder 41)
    - Francisco Monaldi (Poli Science) Field Research Grants Summer 1999 (Box 17, Folder 42)
    - Constanza Ocampo (Anthro Sciences) Field Research Grants Summer 1999 (Box 17, Folder 43)
    - Melissa Minor (Medicine) Field Research Grants Summer 1999 (Box 17, Folder 44)
    - Jaime Paiva (LAS) Field Research Grants Summer 1999 (Box 17, Folder 45)
    - Paula Razquin (Education) Field Research Grants Summer 1999 (Box 17, Folder 46)
    - Diana Rhoten (Education) Field Research Grants Summer 99 (Box 17, Folder 47)
    - Amanda Risser (Medicine) Field Research Grants Summer 1999 (Box 17, Folder 48)
    - Karen Sue Rolph (Anthro Sci) 1999 Summer Field Research (Box 17, Folder 49)
    - Mary Speck (History) Field Research Grants Summer 1999 (Box 17, Folder 50)
    - Eve Zaritsky (Medicine) Field Research Grants Summer 1999 (Box 17, Folder 51)
    - Manuel Vargas (Philosophy) Field Research Grants Summer 1999 (Box 17, Folder 52)
    - Melanie Watkins (Medicine) Field Research Grants Summer 1999 (Box 17, Folder 53)
    - Kyle Van Houtan (Bio Sciences) Field Research Grants Summer 1999 (Box 17, Folder 54)
    - Carlos Suarez (Eng. Econ. Systems) Field Research Grants Summer 1999 (Box 17, Folder 55)
    - Alberto Simpser (Poli Science) Field Research Grants Summer 1999 (Box 17, Folder 56)
    - Cagan Sekercioglu Summer 1999 Field Research Grants Biological Sciences (Box 17, Folder 57)
    - Michael Clarke (Mechanical Eng) Field Research Grants Summer 1999 (Box 17, Folder 58)
    - Reini Jensen (Medicine) Field Research Grants Summer 1999 (Box 17, Folder 59)
    - Steve Mckenna (Medicine) Field Research Grants Summer 1999 (Box 17, Folder 60)
    - Evaluation Sheet/Criteria Summer Field Research (Box 17, Folder 61)
    - 1998 Graduate Summer Field Research (Box 17, Folder 62)
    - Summer Field Research Awardees 1998 (Box 17, Folder 63)
    - Norma Alvarez (Political Science) Field Research Summer 1998 (Box 17, Folder 64)
    - Luis Benveniste Field Research (Education) Summer 1998 (Box 17, Folder 65)
    - Marcelo Bucheli Field Research (History) Summer 1998 (Box 17, Folder 66)
    - Pedro Cabiya Field Research Summer 1998 Spain & Port (Box 17, Folder 67)
    - Martina Faller Field Research (Linguistic) Summer 98 (Box 17, Folder 68)
    - Taryn Fransen Field Research (Earth System) Summer 1998 (Box 17, Folder 69)
    - Esther Gabara (Comp. Lit.) Field Research Summer 1998 (Box 17, Folder 70)
    - Hernan Galperin Field Research (Summer 1998) Communication (Box 17, Folder 71)
    - Soledad Gelles (Span & Port.) Field Research Summer 1998 (Box 17, Folder 72)
    - Marlene Ramirez C (Comp. Lit) Summer 1998 (Box 17, Folder 73)
    - Sybil Rhodes Field Research (Political Sciences) Summer 1998 (Box 17, Folder 74)
    - Amanda Risser Field Research (Medicine) Summer 1998 (Box 17, Folder 75)
    - Karen S. Rolph Summer 1998 Field Research (Anthropology) (Box 17, Folder 76)
    - Victoria Sanford Summer 1998 Field Research (Anthropology) (Box 17, Folder 77)
    - Manuel Vargas Field Research (Philosophy) Summer 1998 (Box 17, Folder 78)
    - Maite Careaga Field Research (Poli Science) Summer 1998 (Box 17, Folder 79)
    - Jackeline Lazu Field Research (Span & Port) Summer 1998 (Box 17, Folder 80)
    - Shoshanna Lurie Field Research (Span & Port.) Summer 1998 (Box 17, Folder 81)
    - Veronica Ocampo Field Research (Anthropology) Summer 1998 (Box 17, Folder 82)
    - Richard Pocklington Field Research (Anthropology) Summer 1998 (Box 17, Folder 83)
    - Elizabeth Zaragoza Field Research (Education) Summer (Box 17, Folder 84)
    - Jim Jung Field Research (Engineering) Summer 1998 (Box 17, Folder 85)
    - Cynthia Alvarez Field Research (Political Science) Summer 1997 (Box 17, Folder 86)
    - Rebecca Bill Summer 1997 (Poli Science) Field Research (Box 17, Folder 87)
    - Zaire Dinzey Flores Field Research (Sociology) Summer 1997 (Box 17, Folder 88)
    - Ross Forman Field Research (Comp. Lit) Summer 1997 (Box 17, Folder 89)
    - Moramay Lopez-Alonso Field Research (History) Summer 1997 (Box 17, Folder 90)
    - Melanie Perez –Ortiz Summer 1997 Field Research (Span & Port) (Box 17, Folder 91)
    - Marisol Negron Summer 1997 (Spanish) Field Research (Box 17, Folder 92)
    - Nathan Zaidenweber Summer 1997 Field Research (Box 17, Folder 93)
    - Undergraduate Summer Field Research Applications (Box 17, Folder 94)
    - Funding for Conference Travel - application (Box 17, Folder 95)
    - Travel Funds for Doctoral Candidates - applications (Box 17, Folder 96)
    - UG Fellowships etc (Box 17, Folder 97)
    - Jesse Adams Summer 1997 Field Research (Box 17, Folder 98)
    - Marcelo Bucheli Field Research Summer 1997 (History) (Box 17, Folder 99)
    - Claudio Duran Summer 1997 Field Research Modern Theater & Lit (Box 17, Folder 100)
    - Valentin Ferdinan Field Research Summer 1997 (Box 17, Folder 101)
    - Esther Gabara Field Research (Comp. Literature) Summer 1997 (Box 17, Folder 102)
    - Jonathan Goldman Field Research (Med School) Summer 1997 (Box 17, Folder 103)
    - Sara Johnson Field Research (Comp. Literature) Summer 1997 (Box 17, Folder 104)
    - Imanol Ordorika Field Research (School of Education) Summer 1997 (Box 17, Folder 105)
    - Bryan de Ponce – Internship in Brazil Summer 1997 (Box 17, Folder 106)
    - David Radel Field Research (Law School) Summer 1997 (Box 17, Folder 107)
    - Diana Rhoten Field Research (Education) Summer 1997 (Box 17, Folder 108)
    - Karen Sue Rolph Field Research (Anthropology) Summer 1997 (Box 17, Folder 109)
    - Paul Schroeder Field Research (Span & Port) Summer 1997 (Box 17, Folder 110)
    - Joao Cezar de Castro Rocha Field Research (Comp. Literature) Summer 97 (Box 17, Folder 111)
    - Ulrike Krostscheck (Classics/Archaeology) Graduate Summer Field Research (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Student Reports (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Miguel Hilario (ANSI) Graduate Summer Field Research 2003 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Carl Fischer (Spanish/ Portugal) (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Christian Mesia (ANSI) (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Maria Helena Rueda (Span/Port) Graduate Summer Field Research 2003 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Luis Perez Hurtado (Law) Graduate Summer Field Research 2003 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Rosaleen O’Gara Graduate Summer Field Research 2003 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Karen Sue Rolph (ANSI) Graduate Summer Field Research 2003 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Alberto Simpser (Political Science) Graduate Summer Field Research 2003 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Nikki Slovak (ANSI) Graduate Summer Field Research 2003 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Emma Stewart (ANSI) Graduate Summer Field Research 2003 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Judith Tonhauser (linguistics) Graduate Summer Field Research 2003 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Dante Angelo (CASA) Graduate Summer Fld Research 03 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Daniel Contreras (ANSI) Graduate Summer Field Research 2003 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Megan Frederickson (Biological Sciences) Graduate Summer Field Research 2003 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - Graduate Summer Field Research 2003 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Vidal Romero (Political Science) Graduate Summer Field Research 2003 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Tim Webmoor (CASA) Graduate Summer Field Research 2003 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - John Wolf (ANSI) Graduate Summer Field Research 2003 (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - Manuel Gomez (Education) Graduate Summer Field Research 2003 (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - Patricia Garcia (Education) Graduate Summer Field Research 2003 (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - Aisha Beliso – De Jesus (CASA) Graduate Summer Field Research 03 (Box 20, Folder 32)
    - David Suarez (Education) Graduate Summer Field Research 2003 (Box 20, Folder 33)
    - Graduate Summer Field Reports 2002 (Box 20, Folder 34)
    - Graduate Summer Field Research 02 (Box 20, Folder 35)
    - 2002 Graduate Summer Field Research (Box 20, Folder 36)
    - Dante Angelo (CASA) 02 Grad Summer Field Research grants (Box 20, Folder 37)
    - Ericka Beckman (Span and Port) 02 Grad Summer Field Research grants (Box 20, Folder 38)
    - Daniel Contreras (ANSI) 02 Field Summer Research (Box 20, Folder 39)
    - Andre de Mello e Souza (Political Science) 02 Summer Field Research grants (Box 20, Folder 40)
    - Megan Frederickson Graduate Summer Field Research 2002 (Box 20, Folder 41)
    - Fernando Armstrong – Fumero Graduate Summer Field Research 2002 (Box 20, Folder 42)
    - Karina Hodoyan (Span and Port) 02 Grad Summer Field Research grants (Box 20, Folder 43)
    - Dana Jensen (ANSI) 02 Grad Summer Field Research (Box 20, Folder 44)
    - Judith Tonhauser (Linguistics) 02 Summer Field Research grants (Grad) (Box 20, Folder 45)
    - Thomas Luschei 2002 Summer FLAS (Box 20, Folder 46)
    - Jai Ranganathan (Biological Sciences) 02 Grad Summer Fld Research grants (Box 20, Folder 47)
    - Sara Rondinel (Span and Port) 02 Grad Summer Fld Research grant (Box 20, Folder 48)
    - Maria Luisa Ruiz (Span and Port) 02 Grad Summer Fld Research grants (Box 20, Folder 49)
    - Ian William Read (History) 2002 Summer Fld Research grants (GRAD) (Box 20, Folder 50)
    - Nicole Slovak (ANSI) 02 Grad Summer Fld Research grants (Box 20, Folder 51)
    - Cagan Sekercioglu (Bio Sciences) 02 Summer Field Research grants (Box 20, Folder 52)
    - Miguel Socias (Education) 02 Grad Summer Field Research (Box 20, Folder 53)
    - Veronica Volny (Biological Sciences) Summer 02 (Baja CA course) (Box 20, Folder 54)
  - Undergraduate Summer Field Research, Subseries 11
    - Benjamin G Fohner UG Service Fellowship 2003 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Daniela Gundling UG Service Fellowship 2003 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Anna Mumford UG Service Fellowship 2003 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Ariel Enfield SKLAR UG Service Fellowship 2003 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Erin Krampetz UG Service Fellowship 2003 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Julie Van Loben Sels UG Service Fellowship 2003 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - UG Service Fellowship 2003 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Kellea Miller UG Service Fellowship 2003 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Amanda Cassel (UG Service Fellowship 2003) (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Kelly Wells UG Service Fellowship 03 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Kaara Baptiste UG Service Fellowship (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Elba Garcia UG Service Fellowship (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Dana Hornbeak UG Service Fellowship (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Julia Nelson UG Service Fellowship (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Lauren Rodriguez UG Service Fellowship (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Marie-Jo Mont-Reynaud UG Service Fellowship (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Rubiana Vaughn UG Service Fellowship (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - John Yandell UG Service Fellowship (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - John Yandell UG Service Fellowship 2 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - UG Field Research 2003 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Fernando Galeana (Economics) UG Field Research 2003 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Abigail Levine (ANSI) UG Summer Field Research 2003 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Christopher Dalton (Public Policy) UG Summer Field Research 2003 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Anna Leticia Mumford (IR) UG Summer Fld Research 2003 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Suzannah Stason/Sarah Shulman UG Research (Winter 03) (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Brinda Thomas / Kellea Miller UG Research (Winter 03) (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Jesse Sandoval (IR / Economics) Summer Fld Research 2003 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Daniela Gundling (LAS UG Summer Fld Research 2003) (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - 2002 UG Summer Field Research (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Nat Corey-Moran UG Summer Field Research 02 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Karis Eklund (ANSI) UG Summer Field Research 2002 (Late Award) Winter (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Jared Grose UG Summer Field Research 2002 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Robert Jack UG Summer Field Research 2002 (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Derek D. Jackson UG Summer Field Research 2002 (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Agustin E. Juarez UG Summer Field Research (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - Matt Kraft UG Summer Field Research 2002 (Box 18, Folder 36)
    - Jessica M. Jenkins UG Summer Field Research 2002 (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - Abigail Ruth Levine UG Summer Field Research (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - Regina Richter UG Summer Field Research 2002 (Box 18, Folder 39)
    - Julie Ruvolo UG Summer Field Research 2002 (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - Susannah Stason UG Field Research (Winter) 02-03 (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - Sarah Schulman UG Field Research (Box 18, Folder 42)
    - Faculty Summer Research – Jorge Ruffinelli (Box 18, Folder 43)
    - Flora Lu Halt – Summer 02 (Box 18, Folder 44)
    - Fernando Gomez – Summer 02 (Box 18, Folder 45)
    - John Rick – Field Research (Box 18, Folder 46)
    - Lyris Wiedemann – Field Research (Box 18, Folder 47)
    - Instructors (faculty grants) (Box 18, Folder 48)
    - Prof. Beatriz Magaloni (Box 18, Folder 49)
    - Prof. Zephyr Frank (Box 18, Folder 50)
    - Prof. Susan Cashion (Box 18, Folder 51)
    - Prof Patrice G. Marks (Box 18, Folder 52)
    - Avi Tuschman (undergraduate) 2001 Summer Field Research (Box 18, Folder 53)
    - Tess Bridgeman (undergraduate) 2001 Summer Field Research (Box 18, Folder 54)
    - Dana Gundling Undergraduate 2001 Summer Field Research (Box 18, Folder 55)
    - Rohan Radhakrishna Summer Field Research 2001 (Box 18, Folder 56)
    - Tress Goodwin (undergraduate) 2001 Summer Field Research (Box 18, Folder 57)
    - Abeo Anderson (undergraduate) 2001 Summer Field Research (Box 18, Folder 58)
    - 2000-2001 Undergraduate Summer Field Research (Box 18, Folder 59)
    - Emily Yates – Doerr (Undergrad) 2000 Summer Field Research (Box 18, Folder 60)
    - Avi Tuschman (Undergraduate) 2000 Summer Field Research (Box 18, Folder 61)
    - Sean Joy (Undergraduate) 2000 Summer Field Research (Box 18, Folder 62)
    - Undergraduate Service Fellowship (Box 18, Folder 63)
    - Tanya Perez (Undergraduate) 2000 Summer Field Research (Box 18, Folder 64)
    - Marcela Paquin (Undergraduate) 2000 Summer Field Research (Box 18, Folder 65)
    - Kimberly McClure (Undergraduate) 2000 Summer Field Research (Box 18, Folder 66)
    - Tess Bridgeman U.G. Service Fellowship 2002 (Box 18, Folder 67)
    - Andrea Osborn U.G. Service Fellowship 2002 (Box 18, Folder 68)
    - Michelle Rhee Service Fellowship 2002 (Box 18, Folder 69)
    - Leanne Farrel U.G. Service Fellowship 2002 (Box 18, Folder 70)
    - UG Service Internship 2002 (Box 18, Folder 71)
    - Tula C. Orum UG Service Fellowship 2000 (Box 18, Folder 72)
    - 2001 Undergraduate Summer Field Research (Box 18, Folder 73)
    - UG Service Fellowship 2001 (Box 18, Folder 74)
    - Christine Lee Summer 2001 UG Service Fellowship (Box 18, Folder 75)
    - Samantha Crow Summer 2001 UG Service Fellowship (Box 18, Folder 76)
    - Keira Goldstein Summer 2001 UG Service Fellowship (Box 18, Folder 77)
    - Carrie Fathman UG Service Fellowship 2000 (Box 18, Folder 78)
    - Matthew Light-Oglander UG Service Fellowship 2000 (Box 18, Folder 79)
    - Anamaria Nino-Murcia UG Service Fellowship 2000 (Box 18, Folder 80)
    - Isela Rosales UG Service Fellowships 2000 (Box 18, Folder 81)
    - Tess Bridgeman UG Service Fellowship 2000 (Box 18, Folder 82)
    - Matt Evans UG Service Fellowship 2000 (Box 18, Folder 83)
    - Emilee Wilhem UG Service Fellowship 2000 (Box 18, Folder 84)
    - Tor Sandven UG Service Fellowship 2000 (Box 18, Folder 85)
    - Mariama White-Hammond UG Service Fellowship 2000 (Box 18, Folder 86)
    - 1999 Undergraduate Summer Field Research (Box 18, Folder 87)
    - Antonia Welch (Undergraduate) 1999 Summer field Research (Box 18, Folder 88)
    - Amanda Garcia (Undergraduate) 1999 Summer Field Research (Box 18, Folder 89)
    - Alexander Nixon (Undergraduate) 1999 Summer Field Research (Box 18, Folder 90)
    - Rachel Steinhart CHRIA Trip 1/99 (Box 18, Folder 91)
    - Katherine Wiatt (Undergraduate) 1999 Summer Field Research (Box 18, Folder 92)
    - Shauna Harrison (Undergraduate) 1999 Summer Field Research (Box 18, Folder 93)